hey guys rexin here this is a short
guide a crash course on how to play giny
so let's just go straight into it I have
a plane to catch in a few hours for a
week's break so I'll be seeing you guys
after that anyway for jiny she's a
broadword user spectral DPS so her combo
looks like this for hit combo and you
notice how her resonance skill lights up
after the fourth hit so this is what you
do do four hits and then you press skill
and she will go up in the air and then
it'll change again to a five hit combo
ending with a plunge so let me repeat
that again on the ground for hit combo
press e go up just Spam basic
again and then she'll finish with plunge
and then finish it off with skill
again so this is the dragon Beam at the
end of the combo so that's basically her
whole chain really easy to play so to
sum
just basic until skill glows basic again
until the skill glows again so basic
skill
glow e spam basic until it glows again
like that so you don't exactly have to
do the full chain you could just press
it once it glows and that's it for a
basic and then for her Liberation skill
straight up
nuke so you already know how to play
jiny on on the field basically that when
she goes up she's a bit like lingy her
hit box is in the
air and you can also use grappling hook
and abuse this so you can do
this and then press
e and grappling hook and do this so
she's safe in the air and then just do
the beam on
them all right that's how you play jiny
that's her rotation now let's move on to
her skills and how she works with her
team so now as for her forte gauge you
see this gauge down here this comprises
of up to 50 points and each point will
buff that Dragon beam in her skill
resonance skill so it's going to buff
this attack right here the one where it
goes up and then four
hits this one it's going to buff this
doing like meme of amounts of damage
lots of damage and how to fill this
gauge
basically as long as she's off the
field any attack from any element will
give one point to it to put it really
simply each element has their own
internal 3se second cool down that's the
first effect and for the second effect
on how points are gained is coordinated
attacks just like Vina's ultimate Yin
Lin's uh punishment Mark and even yuu so
yuu is the best guy for most teams it's
like the most accessible since everyone
has ywu and he builds really fast so the
ideal team for jiny I would say would be
this you start with yenu and then you
alternate between Vina and jiny so the
interesting thing here is that yuu will
be using the healing
set over here five set healing could be
anything plus zero is fine the core
thing is he needs this weapon this blue
weapon originite type four so every
basic attack he's going to trigger
healing and that's going to be enough to
trigger the whole healing
set and his job will be just hitting
once doing his resident skill to place
the wedge down and then doing his Echo
this Turtle Echo so that the rest of the
team get attack buff and then after that
the remaining two characters the middle
character will be using energy set so
Vina would be really good if you don't
have Vina
even Rover is good Yin is good anybody
as long as they hold energy set and then
after that will be jiny with her GS set
so for jiny 43311 build is fine 44111 is
also good 44111 is easy to build as well
so 44 would be J and morning eggs like
so and then 111 and if you got her
jiny's weapon ages of harvest which is
crit rate you can go both crit damage
for the four cost pieces crit damage and
then the rest would be attack attack and
if you using three cost you can go
spectral and attack or spectral spectral
if you're doing four four then for
morning xgs you can also go like crit
damage double crit damage and then she's
going to have really high crit damage
with the right sub stats so to
demonstrate this first team right here
let me just empty her gauge yeah you can
you can do the combo outside of combat
like this it's yellow we're going to
shoot this
guy and then you'll see how fast it
charges I'm just going to put Yu
out press the E switch
Arena and then look at jinc
gaug so that's how you charge it
coordinated
attacks and then press e again for the
beam
and then y again hit once press e press
Q for Echo Marina renew the
Buffs Jin C again look at our Forte
charging really
fast and that's pretty much it for this
team like this is the I would say the
most recommended team to play jiny
effectively really sustain DP PS so to
emphasize on the importance of this
Forte this 50 points Forte it's called
the in
incandescence why the reason this is
good is because for each point let's say
I am at level eight for each point it
gives 38% for each point so imagine
times 50 of this that's why the beam
hits so hard and for giny she primarily
uses resonance skill stat so if you're
building Echo for her look out for
resonance skill damage and the usual
crit damage crit rate and attack percent
so the more resonance skill damage you
have the more meme her beam becomes
actual meme beam Dre Biden
blast so that's pretty much it for
building jiny like this is just the
basics I don't really have much time to
go through the nuances if you guys have
your own tips feel free to drop it in
the comments the other team that you can
run her with would be this one so Vina
healing set tchi energy set and
giny spectral set this one's more for S2
and above let's take a look at her
sequences so S1 just damage the one you
want to look at is S2 so gin C restores
50 incandessence while staying out of
combat for more than 4 seconds this
effect can only be triggered one one
time every 4 seconds this only triggers
outside of combat basically what this
means is is that every time at the start
of every new combat ginc will get a head
start 50 full gauge straight away like
maximum laser 100K like minimum 100K
damage even with like really crappy gear
this is stronger than most people think
like people say oh it it only works
outside of combat it's not that good no
it really is good basically you get a
head start in anything like Tower
hologram you can just drop a nuke on
them straight away without needing to
build it so if you ask me The Sweet Spot
to stop at for jiny for Dolphin maybe
like spender S2 S2 is the best place to
stop any further will just strengthen
that beam even more like S5 is Ultimate
damage and S6 even more uh resonance
skill damage 45% and then even more
multiplier increased by another 45% of
incandescence so yeah that's pretty much
it for
jiny pretty simple
so to recap basic press E when it's
available basic four times on it once
it's glowing press e
again that's the meme beam uses up all
the gauge and then
ultimate and that's pretty much it as
for her main Echo definitely use jer jer
is her main Echo it's a summon Echo
instead of transformation free damage
you don't have to do anything it also
gives her resonance skill so always pop
je first before doing her skills so even
this attack in midair it's all Resident
skill stack all the Resident
skill so yeah she's really versatile to
play and works in almost any team and
that's it guys that's how you play jiny
if you have any questions just post it
in the comments and I hope this guide
has been helpful to you consider leaving
a like comment subscribe to the channel
and I'll see you in the next video
bye-bye
hold